What if a liquidity pool could play the
World Cup?
This is Mundial — a Uniswap v4 hook on X
Layer. It doesn't pick one match or trust
an admin. It runs the entire tournament —
with no one in charge.
Fans pledge one of eight teams — once,
irreversibly. When their team's match is
live, every swap becomes a shot on goal.
Volume scores goals. The market plays the
football.
Watch it run. Argentina versus France —
fans trade, goals go up.
Five to three — Argentina advance.
Brazil against England is scoreless into
extra time. One Brazilian fan swaps…
GOLDEN GOAL.
The match settles inside the very swap
that scored it.
Semifinals, penalties decided by shot
counts, a final — and a champion is
crowned. All of it, hook storage.
One dynamic-fee pool. Fans pay lower fees
— a quarter percent, dropping to
point-one-five while their team plays.
A zero-point-two percent skim builds the
Champions Pot. Winning fans claim it
pro-rata; leftovers go to the LPs.
No owner. No oracle. No randomness. The
only inputs are swaps and time.
Seventy-seven tests. Fuzzed.
Deployed on X Layer. Code public on
GitHub.
Mundial. Live on X Layer. The pool that
plays the World Cup.