What if a liquidity pool could play the
World Cup?
This is Mundial, a Uniswap V4 hook on X
Layer.
Mundial does something harder.
It runs the entire tournament with no one
in charge. Here's the trick.
Fans pledge one of eight teams — once,
irreversibly.
When their team's match is live, every
swap they make becomes a shot on goal.
Trading volume scores goals.
The market literally plays the football.
Watch it run.
Argentina versus France. Fans trade. Goals
go up. Five to three.
Argentina advance.
Brazil against England is scoreless into
extra time. Sudden death.
One Brazilian fan swaps. GOLDEN GOAL.
The match settles inside the very swap
that scored it.
Semifinals.
Penalties decided by shot counts.
A final and a champion is crowned.
All of it, hook storage.
Under the hood, one dynamic fee pool.
Fans pay lower fees, a quarter percent
dropping to 0.15 while their team plays.
A 0.2% skim on fan swaps builds the
Champions Pot.
Winning fans claim it pro-rata to their
volume.
Leftovers are donated to the LPs.
No owner, no oracle, no randomness.
The only inputs are swaps and time.
38 tests, fuzzed.
Mundial, live on X Layer, the pool that
plays the World Cup.